<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Lilly Chin</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Lilly Chin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crafting</title>
      <link>/projects/crafting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/crafting/</guid>
      <description>Cross-Stitching I started cross-stitch in Dec. 2019, because of this Shitpost Sampler goose pattern sent to me by a friend. I was so taken by it that I taught myself from online resources in order to learn how to make it. This started a near addiction in me, especially as I found myself with a lot of time and screen burnout from the COVID-19 pandemic. Since most of my traditional hobbies became off limits, cross-stitching quickly became my go-to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making</title>
      <link>/projects/making/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/making/</guid>
      <description>This page is under construction. For now, enjoy my notes from the previous iteration of the website for what to include. All of these are from undergrad, so I may not include any of these moving forwards. I might just have them as an image gallery setup or a CV of failures.
Github:
Main Old Very Old (FIRST Robotics) Proud (in undergrad) Projects
This website! Lovingly hand-coded since 2016 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>/projects/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/writing/</guid>
      <description>Professional Pieces One of several stories solicited by The Nation &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Campuses Across the Country Are Closing—These Are the Students Impacted&amp;rdquo;, March 16, 2020 Pitched and published a piece for The Bitter Southerner. Please contact me for more details. Amateur Pieces This space is reserved for my own writing. Interviews with me about these events can be found on my press page. My writing about my Jeopardy experiences has been moved to here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
