<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Lilly Chin</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Lilly Chin</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/projects/exmachina/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/exmachina/</guid><description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html> Ex Machina **01** Book of Sand [[02]] Book of Fire [[17]] Book of Glass [[21]] **02** The book that you read, seeking something [[60]] The book that you write, to discover [[52]] The book for which they burn you. [[35]] The book the bacteria write in your bones. [[08]] **03** Please be aware of these risks [[19]] Do not operate without [[14]] Acknowledge the potential for failure. [[18]] When I looked at the sky, I saw clouds forming chains.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>/bio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/bio/</guid><description>Link to high-res headshot Short Biography Lillian Chin is an Assistant Professor at UT Austin in the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering. She received her SB, SM, and PhD from MIT in Electrical Engineering and Computer Science. Her research interests include designing novel robot sensors and actuators, algorithmically generating mechanisms, enhancing robotic manipulation through tactile sensing, and deploying participatory design-based robots in real-world communities.
Long Biography Lillian Chin is an Assistant Professor and a Texas Instruments / Jack Kilby Fellow in the University of Texas, Austin&amp;rsquo;s Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering and a core member of the Texas Robotics Consortium.</description></item><item><title>About This Site</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>This site is a hybrid of Jonathan McGlone&amp;rsquo;s website in Jekyll and Yihui Xie&amp;rsquo;s XMin template for Hugo. I ported most of my old Bootstrap + Jekyll website to a version where I try to
understand every line of code rather than copy-pasting wholesale minimize Javascript usage make the website accessible to screen readers make the website accessible to low bandwidth users Please let me know if you have some recommendations for how to better achieve those goals.</description></item><item><title>Contact Me</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Note on ChatGPT I discourage using ChatGPT to email me because
I can usually tell the writing style is hella annoying purple prose (link) it robs you of a chance to develop your own writing skills If you must use it, please ask for it to give you a very concise email and don&amp;rsquo;t just paste in the four paragraphs it spat out to you. I&amp;rsquo;d always prefer to see a email with many grammar mistakes than a generated email.</description></item><item><title>Crafting</title><link>/projects/crafting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/crafting/</guid><description>Cross-Stitching I started cross-stitch in Dec. 2019, because of this Shitpost Sampler goose pattern sent to me by a friend. I was so taken by it that I taught myself from online resources in order to learn how to make it. This started a near addiction in me, especially as I found myself with a lot of time and screen burnout from the COVID-19 pandemic. Since most of my traditional hobbies became off limits, cross-stitching quickly became my go-to.</description></item><item><title>Making</title><link>/projects/making/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/making/</guid><description>This page is under construction. For now, enjoy my notes from the previous iteration of the website for what to include. All of these are from undergrad, so I may not include any of these moving forwards. I might just have them as an image gallery setup or a CV of failures.
Github:
Main Old Very Old (FIRST Robotics) Proud (in undergrad) Projects
This website! Lovingly hand-coded since 2016 2.</description></item><item><title>Press</title><link>/press/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/press/</guid><description>Robotics Research Mainstream Outlets BBC &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;The robot that sorts out recycling&amp;rdquo; Reuters &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Robot identifies recycling with a squeeze&amp;rdquo; VICE News &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;The Future of Work: A VICE special report&amp;rdquo; Scientific American &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Can Robots Help Pick Up After the Recycling Crisis?&amp;rdquo; CNBC &amp;ndash; Why the United States is Turning to Recycling Robots&amp;quot; Tech Outlets AZO Robotics &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;The Development of an Algorithm that Helps Soft Robots Understand Their Surroundings&amp;rdquo; Venture Beat &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;MIT robot sorts recycling and trash by touch&amp;rdquo; TechCrunch &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;MIT&amp;rsquo;s recycling sorting robot can &amp;lsquo;feel&amp;rsquo; the difference between materials Engadget &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Recycling robot can sort paper and plastic by touch&amp;rdquo; CNET &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Grabby MIT robot sorts recycling by squeezing it&amp;rdquo; Hackaday &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;This Bot Might Be The Way To Save Recycling&amp;rdquo; BostInno &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Meet ROCycle, MIT&amp;rsquo;s New Robot That Helps Sort Recyclable Waste&amp;rdquo; Affiliated Coverage Schmidt Science Fellows &amp;ndash; TEMP MIT News &amp;ndash; Researchers&amp;rsquo; algorithm designs soft robots that sense MIT Technology Review &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;This robot can sort recycling by giving it a squeeze&amp;rdquo; MIT News &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Robots that can sort recycling&amp;rdquo; MIT CSAIL News &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Robots that can sort recycling&amp;rdquo; MIT CSAIL News &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Materials that can change size and shape by twisting&amp;rdquo; Jeopardy I won the 2017 Jeopardy College Championship, which led me to getting a lot of media attention, especially for my memetic Final Jeopardy response.</description></item><item><title>Research Philosophy</title><link>/research/philosophy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/research/philosophy/</guid><description>Slide from my dissertation, highlighting how disability thinking can inform building robots.
Bodies and the Built Environment In sci-fi, we imagine robots to be close companions to humans, living and working alongside us. However, real robots are quite far from this goal, including high-profile accidents such as a surveillance robot running over a toddler in 2016 or a chess-playing robot breaking a child&amp;rsquo;s finger in 2022. I argue that this is because current robot bodies are not well-suited for the environments that we place them in.</description></item><item><title>Who Taught Me</title><link>/research/who-taught-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/research/who-taught-me/</guid><description>Inspired by Aimi Hamraie&amp;rsquo;s list of who taught them, I&amp;rsquo;d like to make a (non-exhaustive) list of the people and things who taught me how to be a person and a researcher. Doing this is my way of fighting the great man theory approach that still tends to dominate academic framings. Academia provides precious little avenues to acknowledge and validate all of the people, labor and resources that shaped us, so here&amp;rsquo;s a page to celebrate the &amp;ldquo;interdependent researcher&amp;rdquo;!</description></item><item><title>Writing</title><link>/projects/writing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/writing/</guid><description>Professional Pieces One of several stories solicited by The Nation &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Campuses Across the Country Are Closing—These Are the Students Impacted&amp;rdquo;, March 16, 2020 Pitched and published a piece for The Bitter Southerner. Please contact me for more details. Amateur Pieces This space is reserved for my own writing. Interviews with me about these events can be found on my press page. My writing about my Jeopardy experiences has been moved to here.</description></item></channel></rss>